{
    "subject": "resource/Martha_Coakley",
    "predicate": "ontology/governor",
    "object": "resource/Deval_Patrick",
    "human_readable": "Martha Coakley was the governor of Deval Patrick.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9056330323219299,
            "question": "Did Martha Coakley and Deval Patrick serve together in government?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8219989538192749,
            "question": "In what state was Deval Patrick the governor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8152130246162415,
            "question": "Who served as governor after Deval Patrick?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7694778442382812,
            "question": "Who was the governor before Deval Patrick?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7549391984939575,
            "question": "Was Martha Coakley a politician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6568168997764587,
            "question": "What years did Deval Patrick serve as governor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5922727584838867,
            "question": "What political position did Martha Coakley hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5174235701560974,
            "question": "Can you name another political position held by Martha Coakley?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1625089794397354,
            "question": "What is the role of a governor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.060927264392375946,
            "question": "What are some key responsibilities of a governor?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Martha Coakley was the governor of Deval Patrick.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4887_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the role of a governor?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4887_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name another political position held by Martha Coakley?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4887_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What political position did Martha Coakley hold?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4887_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4887_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4887_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4887_162.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4887_185.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4887_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4887_206.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4887_211.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4887_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4887_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4887_46.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'} \n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while Martha Coakley and Deval Patrick are mentioned together in various contexts, there is no information to suggest that Coakley was the governor at any point, let alone during or under the tenure of Deval Patrick."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not support the statement that Martha Coakley was the governor of Deval Patrick. Instead, it is mentioned that Deval Patrick was the current Governor when Martha Coakley was running for re-election as a Democratic candidate in Massachusetts."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Martha Coakley was not the governor of Deval Patrick. In the provided context, Martha Coakley is a candidate for governor, but she has not yet been elected as governor and currently, Deval Patrick is the incumbent governor.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several pieces of text state that Deval Patrick was the governor and Martha Coakley was running to be governor, not that Coakley *was* the governor.  Additionally, it says Patrick would not seek re-election in 2014, implying he held the office at that time.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "the context information states \"Martha Coakley, Deval Patrick\" as if they are running together for governor, but later mentions them campaigning separately and having disagreements on issues.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Martha Coakley was not the governor of Deval Patrick; she was a Democratic candidate running for governor against him. At the time mentioned in the context, Deval Patrick was the current governor, and Martha Coakley was his opponent in the gubernatorial race.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}